sweet-page.com 2015-10-15

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

ELEX’s privacy policies explain how we treat your personal data and protect your privacy when you use our Services. By using our Services, you agree that ELEX can use such data in accordance with our privacy policies.

We collect information to provide better services to all of our users – from figuring out basic stuff like which language you speak, to more complex things like which app you’ll find most useful.

Information we get from your use of our services:

 **Device information**

We may collect device-specific information (such as your hardware model, operating system version, unique device identifiers, and mobile network information including phone number). ELEX may associate your device identifiers or phone number with your ELEX Account.

 **Log information**

When you use our services or view content provided by ELEX, we may automatically collect and store certain information in server logs. This may include:

details of how you used our service, such as your search queries.

device event information such as crashes, system activity, hardware settings, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and referral URL.

 **Unique application numbers**

Certain services include a unique application number. This number and information about your installation (for example, the operating system type and application version number) may be sent to ELEX when you install or uninstall that service or when that service periodically contacts our servers, such as for automatic updates.

 **Cookies and anonymous identifiers**

We use various technologies to collect and store information when you visit a ELEX service, and this may include sending one or more cookies or anonymous identifiers to your device. We also use cookies and anonymous identifiers when you interact with services we offer to our partners, such as advertising services or ELEX features that may appear on other sites.

 **How we use information we collect**

We use the information we collect from all of our services to provide, maintain, protect and improve them, to develop new ones, and to protect ELEX and our users. We also use this information to offer you tailored content – such as giving you more useful apps and information.

We use information collected from cookies and other technologies, like pixel tags, to improve your user experience and the overall quality of our services. For example, by saving your language preferences, we’ll be able to have our services appear in the language you prefer.

ELEX processes personal information on our servers in many countries around the world. We may process your personal information on a server located outside the country where you live.

Where we can provide information access and correction, we will do so for free, except where it would require a disproportionate effort. We aim to maintain our services in a manner that protects information from accidental or malicious destruction. Because of this, after you delete information from our services, we may not immediately delete residual copies from our active servers and may not remove information from our backup systems.

We also have security measures (such as firewall protection on our servers and PC's) installed to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the user information under our control.

Users should also be aware of the following:

a. The details users elect to post during the registration procedure or thereafter become the property of ELEX upon receipt by ELEX;

b. ELEX checks for the following information when using ELEX software: your operating system, ELEX Software version, browser version, connectivity, and information regarding your use and the configuration of the ELEX Software ("Parameters") . Parameters are collected in order to provide you with the Software and Services subject to the provisions of this privacy policy hereof and of the ELEX's License Agreement (the "License"), as well as in order to verify that the terms and conditions of the License are not being violated;

c. ELEX gathers information related to our users' use of the our Software (''Usage Patterns'') to better understand how such users, as a group, use the software and the various features thereof, as well as to help ELEX tailor offerings to user groups with specific profiles, and to conduct market research. The Parameters and the Usage Patterns may be used in the aggregate for commercial purposes, including without limitation, for marketing, co-registration to other services, promotional activities or any other activity, including, without limitation, the protection of ELEX's proprietary and other rights all subject to the provisions herein.
